woodweb.com 2006-06-26

# WOODWEB's Privacy Policy

Your use of the WOODWEB Web Site or Services constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and consent to the terms herein and in the User Agreement. Unless otherwise defined in this privacy policy, the defined terms shall have the meaning set forth in the User Agreement.

**Introduction**

WOODWEB is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to the Site. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein.

This privacy policy details our commitment to protect your information and the limited manner in which we will use that information to provide and improve our provision of Services.

**Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy**

Throughout this privacy policy we use several specialized terms. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that tells us specifically who you are, like your name, street address, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. "User Information" means all Personally Identifiable Information and any other forms of information discussed in this privacy policy, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address of a user's computer. We use the term "aggregate" when we combine information from various persons or users. Information is said to be "anonymized" if it does not identify individual persons or entities or associate a particular person or entity with such information.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

If you visit the Site to browse, we will only collect and store the domain name and host from which a user accessed the Internet (e.g., aol.com), the IP address of the user's computer, the user's browser software and operating system, the date and time the user accesses the Site and the Internet address of any Web Site from which the user linked directly to our Site or to which the user links after visiting our Site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to sections of our Sites, to determine from where our visitors linked and to where our visitors link from the Sites and to help us make our Sites more useful. For example, we organize and analyze IP addresses so that we can provide efficient service, enhance security, monitor appropriate usage and produce traffic volume statistics. This type of information is sometimes shared with third parties, such as when we aggregate and disclose Site traffic information for marketing and commercial purposes.

If you send us communications, then we may collect and archive such communications in a file specific to you. If you send communications through the Site, then we may collect and archive such communication.

We use the information we collect from you to build features that we hope will make our Services more attractive and easier for you to use. This may include better customer support and timely notice of new Services. We may share User Information with our partners, affiliates joint venturers and advertisers that are committed to serving your need for our Services and improving your user experience. We may also share aggregate anonymized data relating to activity on the Site and use of our Services, such as demographical and statistical information, for marketing, research and other purposes.

As set forth in our User Agreement and in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law, WOODWEB may but is not obligated to, monitor and review any activity, content and User Information for violation of WOODWEB policies and/or violation of any law or regulation. WOODWEB may also, but is not obligated, to monitor and review User Information to investigate any suspected or reported violation of applicable policies, laws or regulations. Furthermore, User Information may be disclosed to law enforcement or other government officials if appropriate for your protection or in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or our users to legal liability.

**If You Do Not Wish to Disclose User Information**

If you do not want to provide us with certain User Information then you may opt out by not using the Service that provides us with such User Information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that our site can send to your browser for storage on your hard drive. Cookies can make your use of our site easier by saving your status and preferences upon visits to our site. The cookies are refreshed every time you enter the site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. We use cookies to enable WOODWEB to customize information for certain segments of its customer base.

**Third Parties**

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of User Information collected by WOODWEB. If you disclose information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of such information regardless of their affiliation or relationship with WOODWEB. Because WOODWEB does not control the privacy practices of third parties you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those third parties. When you link to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that Web site. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policy before you disclose your personal information to third parties.

We do not try to control, and disclaim responsibility for, information provided by other users or third parties that is made available through our Site. Such information may contain errors, intentional or otherwise, or may be offensive, inappropriate or inaccurate, and in some cases will be mislabeled or deceptively labeled.

**Merger, Assets, Sales, etc.**

If WOODWEB or any of its lines of business is sold, pledged or disposed of as a going concern whether by merger, sale of assets, bankruptcy or otherwise, then the user database of WOODWEB could be sold as part of that transaction and all User Information accessed by such successor or purchaser.

**How do I Contact WOODWEB**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you can contact WOODWEB at [info@woodweb.com](mailto:info@woodweb.com).

**Miscellaneous**

WOODWEB may from time to time change this privacy policy with or without notice, so please check it regularly for any changes or updates. For future reference, WOODWEB will make a link to the current privacy policy available to you on your screen when you are on our Site. Your use of the Site or Services constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and User Agreement and your assent to any modification thereto.
